[music]
>> The 2026 Pro Day at Notre Dame is
complete. [music]
Got a chance to see a lot of guys work
out, see a lot of guys put in their
final impression for [music] NFL teams.
And obviously big names attended Pro
Day. Now, the biggest name here, running
back Jeremiah Love. He did not work out.
He did all his work at the NFL Combine.
He ran the 40 in 4.36 seconds. He ran
for nearly 1,400 yards and 18 rushing
touchdowns last season at Notre Dame.
Saints might have an opportunity with
him, and Saints had some conversations
with him. But he is a guy who's going
high off the board.
>> You know, I've talked to the running
back coach. I've talked to basically
their whole coaching staff. They're
really great people over there. You
know, I would love to be a part of that
organization. Uh I feel like I would
bring a lot to the team. That's all it
was with the Saints. Hopefully, they
like me. Hopefully, they pick me if I'm
there. His running back teammate, Kyren
Williams, did do some drills for NFL
teams. He ran for about 1,700 yards in
his career at Notre Dame, 21 touchdowns.
But notable for Williams, returned 22
kickoffs for about 800 yards and three
touchdowns, a valuable commodity in the
NFL. So, he will add value in that
department, and a team might look at him
as a dual threat.
>> A lot of people realize that [music] um
special teams can really change the the
dynamic of a game. Just being able to
change the game with the ball [music] in
my hands, I think it's it's very
important to be versatile. Also, wide
receiver Malachi Fields worked [music]
out. Malachi Fields, 6'4", 220 lb, a
huge target for NFL teams. So, he might
fit nicely with the Saints. We'll see
how that goes in [music] the upcoming
NFL Draft. Whatever vision the the team
has for me, you know, that's what I see
for myself, just coming in and trying to
make an impact anywhere I can. Saints,
by the way, huge representation here at
Pro Day at Notre Dame. We do expect to
see also the Saints coaching contingent
at Ohio State's Pro Day on Wednesday. A
lot of top prospects there, also. I'm
John DeShazier, here in South Bend,
Indiana, at Notre Dame. We will see you
tomorrow from Columbus, Ohio.